{
  "questions": [
    {
      "topic": "t1",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "q1",
          "answer": "a1",
          "points": 100
        },
        {
          "question": "q2",
          "answer": "a2",
          "points": 200
        },
        { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
        { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
        { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 }
      ]
    },

    {
        "topic": "t1",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "q1",
            "answer": "a1",
            "points": 100
          },
          {
            "question": "q2",
            "answer": "a2",
            "points": 200
          },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "topic": "t1",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "q1",
            "answer": "a1",
            "points": 100
          },
          {
            "question": "q2",
            "answer": "a2",
            "points": 200
          },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 }
        ]
      },

      {
        "topic": "t1",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "q1",
            "answer": "a1",
            "points": 100
          },
          {
            "question": "q2",
            "answer": "a2",
            "points": 200
          },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 }
        ]
      },
      {
        "topic": "t1",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "q1",
            "answer": "a1",
            "points": 100
          },
          {
            "question": "q2",
            "answer": "a2",
            "points": 200
          },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 },
          { "question": "q2", "answer": "a2", "points": 200 }
        ]
      }
  ],

  "teams": [
    {
      "team-name": "Champions",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "Varshini",
      "participant2": "Manikanta",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-to": ""
    },
    {
      "team-name": "NOOBS",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "Kshitiz Gangwar",
      "participant2": "Saksham Sharma",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-to": ""
    },
    {
      "team-name": "Tech Titans",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "Hridyansh Sharma",
      "participant2": "Harshit Soni",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-to": ""
    },
    {
      "team-name": "DEADPOOL",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "Pradeep Kumar",
      "participant2": "p2",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-to": ""
    },
    {
      "team-name": "team5",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "p1",
      "participant2": "p2",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-to": ""
    },
    {
      "team-name": "team1",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "p1",
      "participant2": "p2",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-to": ""
    },
    {
      "team-name": "team2",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "p1",
      "participant2": "p2",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-to": ""
    },
    {
      "team-name": "team3",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "p1",
      "participant2": "p2",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-to": ""
    },
    {
      "team-name": "team4",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "p1",
      "participant2": "p2",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-to": ""
    },
    {
      "team-name": "team5",
      "points": 0,
      "participant1": "p1",
      "participant2": "p2",
      "wager-amount": 0,
      "wager-answer": "",
      "wager-to": ""
    }
  ],

  "currentStats": {
    "currQuestion": "",
    "currPoints": ""
  },

  "finalStats": {
    "question": "final question loololololololololo",
    "answer": "askhaklgh",
    "active": 0
  }
}
